Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.2 (1919: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.3 (1919: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.4 (1919: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.5 (1919: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.6 (1919: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.36:no.7 (1919: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.36:no.8 (1919: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.36:no.9 (1919: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.36:no.10 (1919: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.36:no.11 (1919: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1919; Publication (Box 108, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.36:no.12 (1919: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.1 (1920: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.2 (1920: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.3 (1920: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.4 (1920: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.5 (1920: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.6 (1920: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.7 (1920: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.8 (1920: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.9 (1920: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.10 (1920: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.11 (1920: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1920; Publication (Box 109, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.12 (1920: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.1 (1921: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.2 (1921: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.3 (1921: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.4 (1921: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.5 (1921: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.6 (1921: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.38:no.7 (1921: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.38:no.8 (1921: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.38:no.10 (1921: Oct.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.38:no.11 (1921: Nov.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1921; Publication (Box 109, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.38:no.12 (1921: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.1 (1922: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.2 (1922: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.3 (1922: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.4 (1922: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.5 (1922: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.6 (1922: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.6A (1922: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.39:no.7 (1922: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.39:no.8 (1922: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.39:no.9 (1922: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.39:no.10 (1922: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.39:no.11 (1922: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1922; Publication (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.39:no.12 (1922: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 109, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.40:no.1 (1923: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 109, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.40:no.2 (1923: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 109, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.40:no.3 (1923: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 109, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.40:no.4 (1923: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 109, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.40:no.5 (1923: May)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.7 (1923: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.8 (1923: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.9 (1923: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.10 (1923: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.11 (1923: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1923; Publication (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.40:no.12 (1923: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.41:no.1 (1924: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.41:no.2 (1924: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.41:no.3 (1924: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.41:no.4 (1924: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.41:no.5 (1924: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.41:no.5A (1924: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.7 (1924: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.8 (1924: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.9 (1924: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.10 (1924: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.11 (1924: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1924; Publication (Box 110, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.12 (1924: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.1 (1925: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.2 (1925: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.3 (1925: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.4 (1925: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.5 (1925: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.6 (1925: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.7 (1925: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.8 (1925: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.9 (1925: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.10 (1925: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.11 (1925: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1925; Publication (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.12 (1925: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.1 (1926: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.2 (1926: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.3 (1926: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.4 (1926: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.5 (1926: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.6 (1926: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.7 (1926: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.8 (1926: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.9 (1926: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.10 (1926: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.11 (1926: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1926; Publication (Box 110, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.12 (1926: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.44:no.1 (1927: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.44:no.2 (1927: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.44:no.3 (1927: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.44:no.4 (1927: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.44:no.5 (1927: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 110, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.44:no.5A (1927: May)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.6 (1927: June)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.7 (1927: July)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.8 (1927: Aug.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.9 (1927: Sept.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.10 (1927: Oct.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.11 (1927: Nov.)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1927; Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.12 (1927: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.1 (1928: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.2 (1928: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.3 (1928: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.4 (1928: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.5 (1928: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.6 (1928: June)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.45:no.7 (1928: July)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.45:no.8 (1928: Aug.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.45:no.9 (1928: Sept.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.45:no.10 (1928: Oct.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.45:no.11 (1928: Nov.)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1928; Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.45:no.12 (1928: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1929: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1929: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1929: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1929: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.5 (1929: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.6 (1929: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.7 (1929: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.8 (1929: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.9 (1929: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.10 (1929: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.11 (1929: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1929; Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.12 (1929: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.1 (1930: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.2 (1930: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.3 (1930: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.4 (1930: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.5 (1930: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.6 (1930: june)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.7 (1930: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.8 (1930: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.9 (1930: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.10 (1930: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.11 (1930: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1930; Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.12 (1930: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.1 (1931: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.2 (1931: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.3 (1931: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.4 (1931: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.5 (1931: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.6 (1931: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.7 (1931: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.8 (1931: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.9 (1931: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.10 (1931: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.11 (1931: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1931; Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.48:no.12 (1931: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.1 (1932: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.2 (1932: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.3 (1932: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.4 (1932: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.5 (1932: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.6 (1932: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.7 (1932: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.8 (1932: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.9 (1932: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.10 (1932: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.11 (1932: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1932; Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.12 (1932: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.1 (1933: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.2 (1933: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.3 (1933: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.4 (1933: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.5 (1933: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.6 (1933: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.7 (1933: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.8 (1933: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.9 (1933: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.10 (1933: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.11 (1933: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1933; Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.12 (1933: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.1 (1934: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.2 (1934: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.3 (1934: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.4 (1934: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.5 (1934: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.6 (1934: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.7 (1934: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.8 (1934: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.9 (1934: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.10 (1934: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.11 (1934: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1934; Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.51:no.12 (1934: Dec.)
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.1 (1935: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.2 (1935: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.3 (1935: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.4 (1935: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.5 (1935: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.6 (1935: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.7 (1935: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.8 (1935: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.52:no.9 (1935: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1935; Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)